This article is so positive.
这篇文章是如此的正面.
It's glowing.
是高度赞许的.
I can't believe I didn't notice it this morning.
真不敢相信我上午竟没有注意到它.
I love this part:
我喜欢这一段:
"Some public servants do serve the public.
"有些公务员确实是为公众服务的.
State Prosecutor Hobart is one." Wow.
州检察官Hobart就是其中之一."Wow.
What do you think?
你有什么看法?
What can I think? It says here,
我能有什么看法?这儿说了,
"Hobart won an important victory for public health in Massachusetts."
"Hobart为Massachusetts州的公众健康赢得了一个重大的胜利."
You're my hero.
你是我的英雄.
Yeah?
是吗?
I heard Beth boast about you to Justine.
我听见Beth在Justine面前吹嘘你.
In a very cool way, of course.
当然,是以十分平静的语气.
I impressed the house critic.
我给这个房子里的评论家留下了深刻的印象.
That is impressive.
那倒挺激动人心的.
It's just the age, honey.
亲爱的,这只是年龄关系.
It's her job to make us feel old and useless.
她的天职就是就是要让我们感到自己衰老和无用.
You were fifteen once, don't you remember?
你也有过15岁,还记得吗?
I'm afraid that was a long time ago.
恐怕那是很久远以前的事了.
-And I was never...  -Here we go.
-而且我从不...       -又来了.
Did you hear her yesterday?
你昨天听到她说的话了吗?
She told someone on the phone,
她在电话里跟人说,
"My parents are so middle-class."
"我的父母真是太中产阶级了."
What does that mean?
这是什么意思?
I'm sure we were just as bad.
我肯定我们以前比她好不到哪去.
So...
那么...
Yes?
什么?
You do this fabulous job.
你做了一件了不起的工作.
You win this case.
你打赢了这场官司.
Mm-hmm.
People love you.
人们都喜欢你.
You get glowing reviews.
对你称赞不已.
You get praise from your colleagues.
你同事对你也大加赞扬.
I have just one question.
我只有一个问题.
Yes?
什么?
Do you get a raise?
你有没有加薪呢?